整个小组在房间中交织起伏 吟咏着
And the entire group was weaving around the room and chanting.
然后有这么个时候  人们跳起舞
And then at one point, people were dancing...
我当时正和一个姑娘跳
and I was dancing with a girl...
突然间 我们的手开始振动着相互靠拢
and suddenly our hands began vibrating near each other--
就像这样  振动着 振动着
like this --vibrating, vibrating.
于是我们跪下来 我一下子就在她的胳膊中呜咽了
And we went down to our knees, and suddenly I was sobbing in her arms...
而她用胳膊轻轻抱了抱我 然后她也开始哭了
and she was sort of cradling me in her arms, and then she started to cry too.
然后我们-我们拥抱了一会儿
And then we -- then we just hugged each other for a moment.
接着 呃 我们重新加入舞蹈
And, uh, then we joined the dance again.
后来到了某个时候  几个小时后
And then at a certain point, hours later...